

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a computer systems engineer with over 2 years of experience in OOP and multi-paradigm programming languages, and SQL database management systems.

I'm excited about work on a software enterprise to show my knowledge and my skills. I'm looking for the oportunity to raise my professional career and work with my future coworkers to make a quality job to satisfy our clients.

#### CONTACT

+52 672-125-1430



linkedin.com/in/ <u>luisfernandocardenas/</u>



github.com/luizon



If-cardenas@hotmail.com

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish Native

**English** 

Conversational

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

- Videogames development
- Speedrun streamer

# LUIS FERNANDO CÁRDENAS VEGA

Computer Systems Engineer

#### **EDUCATION**

Instituto Tecnológico de Culiacán

Computer systems engineering degree

August 2016 -August 2022

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### SuKarne – Business Inteligence Analyst

August 2023 - Current

- Oracle SQL, SQL Server
- Advance Excel management
- SAP BO y PowerCenter
- Python

## Campus Digital Coppel - Programmer

March 2023 - July 2023

- Backend development
- **SQL** Server

- Legacy programming
- C++ y Java

## CAT Coppel – Systems Analyst

December 2021 - March 2023

- Fullstack development
- SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL

- Desktop development
- Testing
- Java, PHP y Javascript

# **CAT Coppel – Information Processing Analyst**

April 2021 - December 2021

- Reports generation
- PostgreSQL y Javascript
- Ticket solutions
- Web-side apps development

# **CAT Coppel - Telephone executive**

August 2020 - April 2021

- Tickets generation
- Protocol tracking
- Customer attention

#### **EVENTS**

Hacking Minds hackathon

**Assistant** 

Global Game Jam Jammer (Assistant) March 2020

February 2023

## **SKILLS**

- **Javascript**
- Java
- PHP
- HTML
- CSS
- C++
- API RESTful
- XAMPP

- Creativity
- Teamwork
- Detail-oriented
- Quality assurance
- Problem-solving
- Flexibility
- Emotional intelligence